{
    "subject": "resource/Rugrats",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_children's_television_series",
    "human_readable": "Rugrats is about American children's television series.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7337287664413452,
            "question": "What is Rugrats about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4950629472732544,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Rugrats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4625105857849121,
            "question": "What type of program is Rugrats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3709349036216736,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Rugrats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3392683267593384,
            "question": "Where is Rugrats set?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31149595975875854,
            "question": "What age group is Rugrats targeted towards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22204971313476562,
            "question": "When did Rugrats first air?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21868456900119781,
            "question": "Has Rugrats won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21130076050758362,
            "question": "What is the overall tone of Rugrats?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19340290129184723,
            "question": "Is Rugrats still running today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rugrats is about American children's television series.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5781_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall tone of Rugrats?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5781_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Rugrats won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5781_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Rugrats first air?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5781_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5781_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that \"Rugrats\" is an American animated television series focused on the day-to-day lives and adventures of babies or toddlers, which aligns with the statement that it is about an American children's television series."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}